Guide to the New York State Farm Bureau Federation records, [ca. 1918-1968]
New York State Farm Bureau Federation records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State Farm Bureau Federation records, [ca. 1918-1968]
2714
New York State Farm Bureau Federation.
50 cubic ft.,
Correspondence, Legal Documents, Manuscripts, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes administrative and legislative files, files for their annual meetings and those of the American Farm Bureau Federation and the New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations, and extensive standing and ad hoc committee files.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
A conference of farm bureau officers from 34 New York State counties resulted in the founding of the New York State Farm Bureau Federation on February 14, 1917. It's objectives were to encourage cooperation and coordinate and strengthen the work of New York's farm bureau associations. By 1919, every county in New York was represented in the Federation.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes administrative and legislative files, files for their annual meetings and those of the American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF) and the New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations, and extensive standing and ad hoc committee files, containing correspondence, memoranda, reports, legislative bills, questionnaires, clippings, minutes, resolutions, telegrams, and publications of the state and national Federations, which document the development of positions the Federation took on contemporary issues including crop allotment, farm price supports, daylight saving time, state aid for construction of town and county highways, regulations of small slaughtering establishments, the 1961 milk strike in the New York City area, property taxes, relations with cooperative associations, property damage done by hunters, Farm Bureau Insurance Services, and the relationship between the state Federation and the Cooperative Extension Service associated with Cornell University; also, records concerning communication and cooperation with the Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange, (GLF), Kansas State Farm Bureau, Co-operative Association, Dairymen's League, New York State Holstein-Friesian Association, Empire State Potato Growers' Cooperative Association, American Farm Bureau Federation, New York State College of Agriculture at Cornell University, New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations, New York county farm bureaus, and other organizations.
Correspondents include Howard E. Babcock, Charles W. Bassett, C.K. Bullock, Maurice C. Burritt, Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Jay Coryell, H.L. Creal, Roger W. Fleming, Edward S. Foster, John S. Gold, Samuel R. Guard, Hugh F. Hall, J.R. Howard, Jacob K. Javits, Nelson M. Jost, Kenneth B. Keating, Enos Lee, John C. Lynn, Albert R. Mann, H.C. McHenrie, Thomas McKeary, T.E. Milliman, Harold C. Ostertag, J. Don Parel, Charles G. Porter, F.E. Robertson, Nelson A. Rockefeller, L.R. Simons, E.P. Smith, Frank M. Smith, S.L. Stivings, John Taber, H.R. Talmage, Wayne E. Tyler, E. Victor Underwood, E.C. Weatherby, and E.R. Zimmer.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State Farm Bureau Federation.; Babcock, Howard Edward, 1889-1950.; Bassett, Charles W., 1927-; Bullock, Charles Kenneth, 1903-; Burritt, M. C.(Maurice Chase); Byrd, Harry Flood, Jr., 1914-; Coryell, Jay.; Creal, Harold Leroy, 1896-; Fleming, Roger W.; Foster, Edward Shields, 1901-1973.; Gold, John Steiner, 1898-; Guard, Samuel R.; Hall, Hugh F.; Howard, James R., 1873-1954.; Javits, Jacob Koppell, 1904-; Jost, Nelson M.; Keating, Kenneth Barnard, 1900-; Lee, Enos.; Lynn, John C.; Mann, Albert Russell, 1880-1947.; McHenrie, H. C.; McKeary, Thomas, 1870-1948.; Milliman, Thomas E.; Ostertag, Harold Charles, 1896-; Parel, J. Don.; Porter, Charles G.; Robertson, Fred Eugene, 1878-1953.; Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich, 1908-; Simons, Lloyd R., 1886-; Smith, E. P.; Smith, Frank M.; Stivings, S.L.; Taber, John., 1880-1965.; Talmage, Henry R., 1872-1951.; Tyler, Wayne E.; Underwood, E. Victor, 1889-1974.; Weatherby, E. C.; Zimmer, E. R.; American Farm Bureau Federation.; Co-operative Association, Inc.; Cooperative Grange League Federation Exchange, Inc.; Cornell University--Cooperative Extension.; Dairymen's League.; Empire State Potato Growers' Cooperative Association.; Farm Bureau Insurance Services.; Kansas State Farm Bureau.; New York State College of Agriculture.; New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations.; New York State Holstein-Friesian Association.
Subjects:
Agriculture--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Link to a partial finding aid. PDF file. Not all the material in the collection is listed in this guide. (Box 1-33)
- American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF) 1962, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  Recognition and Award Program
- American Agricultural Mutual Insurance Co. Annual Meeting, March 17, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  Chicago, Illinois
- E.S. Foster - Conference of State Farm Bureau Presidents and Administrative Officers, July 16-18 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Proposed RC and D Project Application (Box 34, Folder 4)
  South Central, New York
- Board Meeting, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  E.S. Foster
- Applications for Position of Legislative Assistant, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Site Plan and Site Details for New York Farm Bureau Headquarters Inc., 1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Headquarters Committee, 1960-65 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Discussion Guide, Between 1964-68 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- E.S. Foster Farm Records, 1964-66 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Annual Meeting 1965, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Accouting and Business Meeting, 1964-65 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- E.S. Foster Tire Program, 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- New York Farm Bureau Supply Co. Inc., 1966 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- PD Meeting, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Annual Meeting Material and General Board Meeting, 1964-65 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Eastern Railroads, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Secretary-Treasurer Report Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Board of Directors Meeting, 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Financial Statement New York Farm Bureau Service Co., August 31, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Board of Directors Meeting, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Board of Directors Meeting and E.S. Foster - Marketing, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Documents for E.S. Forester (Executive Secretary) (Box 34, Folder 24)
  Letters, legislative documents, financial statements
- Floor Plan for New York Farm Bureau Offices, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Legislation, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Legislature Opinions to Governor, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Local Government Affortionment, April 1965 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Annual Report, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Annual Report, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- New York Farm Electrification Council, 1966-67 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- American Agricultural Marketing Association, 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Marketing, Bargaining, Negotiations, 1965-66 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  Meeting reports, letters, newsletters, NYFB Marketing Cooperative
- Cornell Documents, 1963-66 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Laws and Politics, 1963-67 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Farm Bureau Statistics, 1960-64 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Oil and Gas, 1962-66 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Taxes, 1956-66 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Supreme Court, 1960-66 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  Antonia Banach vs. Home Gas Company
- Farm Bureau Women, 1963-64 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Cows and Dairy, 1962-66 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Meeting Notes (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Misc. Letters, 1962-66 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Misc. Farm Bureau Documents (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Publications and Books in box 35 (Box 35)
- Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing - Interim Report, 1961 (Box 35)
  Legislative Document, State of New York
- Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing - New Formula Proposal and Staff Studies, 1962 (Box 35)
- Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing - Final Report, 1963 (Box 35)
- A Guide to School District Reorganization for New York State, 1958 (Box 35)
- Educational Testing Service Annual Report 1961-1962, 1961-62 (Box 35)
- Is Education the Business of the Federal Government?, 1964 (Box 35)
  Terry Sanford
- Supplemental Report of Advisory Council on Reapportionment to the Legislature of the State of New York, 1966 (Box 35)
- Elections in Rural New York, 1959 (Box 35)
  New York State College of Agriculture Cornell Extension Bulletin 777, C.A. Bratton and E.A. Lutz)
- Recommendations to the 1967 Constitutional Convention, 1966 (Box 35)
  New York State Educational Conference Board
- Jefferson County's Agriculture: Its Economic Strength, 1963 (Box 35)
  Donald J. White
- Thesis: Some Problems of Town Highway Superintendents in New York State, 1945 (Box 35)
  Charles Thomas Male Jr., Cornell University
- Employment Service Review, 1966 (Box 35)
  U.S. Department of Labor, January 1966
- Stature and Excellence: Focus for the Future, the Master Plan, Revised 1964, 1964 (Box 35)
  State University of New York
- The Bank that Banks Built: the Story of Savings Banks Trust Company 1933-1958, 1959 (Box 35)
  Adolf A. Berle, Jr.
- Compilation of Statutes Relating to Soil Conservation, Marketing Quotas and Allotments, etc., 1959 (Box 35)
  United States Department of Agriculture, Agriculture Handbook No. 158
- New York State's Contribution to the Organization and Development of the County Agent-Farm Bureau Movement, 1957 (Box 35)
  L.R. Simons, Cornell Extension Bulletin 993
- Report on the Temporary Commission on Irrigation 1959, 1959 (Box 35)
  State of New York
- This is Farm Bureau, No Date (Box 35)
  American Farm Bureau Federation (AFBF)
- Agricultural Prices and Cash Receipts from Farm Marketings 1940-1963, 1964 (Box 35)
  U.S. Department of Agriculture and Markets, New York Crop Reporting Service
- Freedom is Our Responsibility, 1962 (Box 35)
  E.H. Fallon
- Services Offered by The Pennsylvania Farmers' Association, No Date (Box 35)
- My Country 'Twas of Thee, 1965 (Box 35)
- Farm Bureau State Policies for 1967, 1966 (Box 35)
  New York Farm Bureau
- Local Finance, 1967 (Box 35)
  Temporary State Commission on the Constitutional Convention
- Agriculture at Cornell, No Date (Box 35)
- Farmworkers: A Reprint from the 1966 Manpower Report, 1966 (Box 35)
  U.S. Department of Labor, W.Willard Wirtz
- Outline of the 1966 New York Farm and Food Processing Labor Program, 1966 (Box 35)
  New York State Interdepartmental Committee on Farm and Food Processing Labor
- Farm Bureau Study Mission to the Common Market: A Report, No Date (Box 35)
- Work Injuries in New York State Agriculture: Characteristics of Accidents and Workmen's Compensation Coverage and Premium Rates, 1961 (Box 35)
- Office for Local Government, 1961-62 (Box 35)
- The Committee for the White House Conference on Education, 1956 (Box 35)
- World Agriculture: Our Challenge, No Date (Box 35)
  Cornell University
- Some Population Changes in New York State, 1950-1950, and Some Implications for Rural Government, 1955 (Box 35)
- Office for Local Government, 1961-62 (Box 35)
- Documents and Files in box 35 (Box 35)
- Multi-State Board Meeting, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- The Standard Form of Agreement Between Owner and Contractor, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  The American Institute of Architects
- Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- New York Farm Bureau, No Date (Box 35, Folder 4)
  E.S. Foster, Taxes, W.E. Howell Associates, Inc., employments, etc.
- Livestock Advisory Council, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Report of the National Committee on Farm Bureau Organization, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Minutes of Meeting and Various Documents, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Minutes of Meeting and Various Documents, 1964-66 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  E.S. Foster, Petition in the Legislature of the State of New York
- Chamber Commerce Ithaca, New York, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Documents from E.S Foster, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  Laws and politics
- Articles, 1961-67 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, Some Trends in United States and New York Agriculture, committee reports, legislative matters, Program II - Project E: Limited Revision of Cooperative Corporations Law,
- Documents and Forms, 1966-67 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  Empire Cooperative, AMTEC Cooperative, Photo of John J. Ryan
- Publications, 1955-67 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Letters, 1955-67 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Cornell University College of Home Economics Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Council, 1958-59 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Cornell Univeristy College of Home Economics Misc. Documents, 1965-66 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  Advisory council, You and Your Family, statistics, summary of appropriations, budget request
- Cornell Univeristy College of Home Economics Misc. Documents, 1962-66 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Summary of appropriations, Admissions Philosophy, Policies, and Procedures on Admissions, council meeting, articles, papers
- Cornell University College of Home Economics Publications, No Date (Box 36, Folder 4)
  List of Publications January 1964, Financing of One-Unit Homeowner Properties, Members of the Council for the New York State College of Home Economics, Careers for Home Economists, Announcements, Endowment Fund Proposal for a Fellowship for Graduate Study, Graduate Study in Home Economic Fields at Cornell University, State Colelge of Home Economics at Cornell University
- Cornell Agronomy Advisory Committee Meetings, 1960-64 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Annual Report to the President of Cornell University 1965-66, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Cornell University College of Agriculture Documents, 1959-66 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  Committee Report on Marketing Program and Policy, Report of the President's Committee, letters, Census of Agriculture 1959 Fulton County, meeting minutes
- Cornell University College of Agriculture Publications, 1961-67 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  Speaking Out on the Great Issues of Agriculture, Agricultural Science Youth Program, Food Marketing: Conflict and Common Interest, Why Study Vocational Agriculture in High School?, Highschool Natural Science Program, At a Glance..., the Drouth of 1962 in New York State
- New York State Cooperative Extension Service Publications and Documents, 1963-65 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  State sales tax, Extension's Role in Education for Living, Changing and Adjusting Agriculture
- New York State Education Publications and Documents, 1960-64 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  ETS, the Revolution in School Mathematics, Local School Boards: Organization and Practices
- New York State Tax Documents, 1959-65 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  Highway Use Tax Law, Truck Mileage Tax Regulations 21
- New York State Minimum Wage, 1951-66 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Chauffeurs and Drivers, 1961-64 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- New York State Dairy, 1963-65 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1962-65 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- New York State Oil and Gas, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- The Kiplinger Washington Letter, 1963-64 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Law and Legislative, 1962-1965 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  New York State Legislature 1961-1962
- New York State Misc. Documents (Box 36, Folder 19)
  Developing New York's Rural Resources, Health Insurance Newsletter, map, Industrial Bulletin, Analysis of Governor Rockefeller's Water
- New York State Farming and Agriculture Publications, 1957-64 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  Report of the Temporary State Commission on Irrigation 1957, Air Photo Study 1964, New York State Field Crops 1949-1963, Department of AGriculture and Markets Annual Report 1961
- Misc. Publications, 1962-66 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  Be Fruitful and Multiply, Charting the Second Century Under the Land-Grant Philosophy of Education, Man the Provider, Threads of Life, pamphlets
- Map: New York State Science Service Oil and Gas Fields and Main GAs Transmission Lines of NY State, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Newsclippings and Photo, 1964-65 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  Ken Bullock
- New York Farm Equipment Dealers Association, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- New York Farm-City Council, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Farm Bureau Education Workshop, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Farm Bureau Tire Service Program - County Kit, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Farm Bureau Tire Service Program - Service Agent Kit, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Medicare 1966, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Farm Bureau Conference Board Dec. 10, 1956, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Board Meeting Apr. 27, 1955, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- E.S. Foster Folder, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Local Government, 1963-64 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Nelson A. Rockefeller, Local Government Operation, Services to Local Governments, Proceedings Municipal Law Seminar
- Agronomy Department Advisory Committee, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Information and Handbook
- Marketing Publications, 1960-63 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  A Market Pool Order for the Combined Marketing Areas, the Challenge of Change in Marketing1
- Farm Bureau Legislative News, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Report No. 1, 3, 4, 7, 8, 9
- Tax Reports, 1960-64 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  An Evaluation of the Appraisal Procedures Being Applied to Taxable State-Owned Forest Lands in New York, Interim Report of New York State Tax Structure Study Committee
- Publications on Changing Agriculture, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  Cornell University, An Adaptive Program for Agriculture, Agriculture's New Dimensions: The Empire State: 1960-1970
- Extension Development Publications, 1955-63 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Extension Organization and Leadership Development, County Extension Service Handbook for Operation Advance, the Beginning of Extension Programs and Their Development Through Leadership, Cornell University
- New York Farm Bureau Marketing Cooperative Binder, 1963-65 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  Marketing finacial report, board meeting minutes, marketing finances, balance sheets
- General Conditions and Specifications of the Office Building for NYFB Headquarters, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Correspondence with Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Motor Vehicles, 1959-65 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  Letters, publications, and articles regarding motor vehicle legislature
- Farm Bureau Insurance Services, 1955-63 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  Letters and newsletters
- Reapportionment of State Legislature, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- List of Cornell Publications, 1964/66 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- New York State Legislative Matters, 1957-66 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  Letters, newsletters, newspaper, directory, map
- New York State Farming, 1957-66 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  Letters, articles, publications
- Advisory Council for the College of Agriculture and the Agricultural Experiment Stations, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  Report by Dean Charles E. Palm, E.S. Foster
- Western New York Clergy Economic Education Conference, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  E.S. Foster, letters
- Misc. Documents and Letters, 1963-67 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  E.S. Foster, the Farmer's Acres, farm bureau egg promotion
- News Clippings, 1953-66 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- New York Farm Bureau History, Information, Statistics, Map, 1950-54 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Welch Grape Juice Company and National Grape Co-operative Association Inc., 1947-56 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  Meeting minutes, production studies, articles, legislative material, news clippings, letters
- New York State Grapes: Costs, Plots, and Figures, 1933-56 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- New York State Grapes: Newsclippings, Statistics, and Figures, 1951-53 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  The Grape Belt, Ken Bullock
- New York State Grapes: Minutes of Meeting, 1952-59 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  Grape Growers and Growers Organization, International Grape Committee, Grape Continuing Committee
- New York State Grapes: Documents 1951-1957, 1951-57 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- New York State Grapes: Documents 1958-1962, 1958-62 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- New York State Grapes: Documents 1962-63, 1962-63 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- New York State Grapes: Documents 1954, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- New York State Grapes: Documents 1965-1967, 1965-67 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- New York State Grapes: Documents 1967-68, 1967-68 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Ontario Grapes and Table of Grapes by State, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Harvest Magazine, Fall 1947, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- New York State Grape Growers Cooperative, 1958-59 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Should Grape Growers Limit New Plantings?, Est. 1961 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  J.J. Sugden
- Canada-US Cherry Meeting, May 25, 1965, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Canada-US Cherry Meeting, June 4, 1963, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- New York Farm Bureau By-Laws and Organization, 1960-61 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Grape Marketing, 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Letters Regarding Ontario Grape Committee, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Grape Marketing, 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  Ken Bullock, Cornell University, Concord Grape Market Structure, Market Development Program For the American Type Grape, surveys, newsletter
- Commercial Grape Growers, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Minutes of Meeting from Various Grape Committees, 1962-63 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  Chautauqua Country, Mayville, Pennsylvania
- New York State Wine Grape Growers, Inc., 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  Canada Agricultural Products Standard Act.: Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Regulations
- Maple Marketing Committee, 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Maple Syrup Commitee of New York Farm Bureau, 1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  Minutes of Meeting, National Maple Syrup Digest
- New York Farm Bureau Potatoes, 1963-64 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  United States Standards for Grades of Potatoes for Processing, Potatoes as a Livestock Feed, meeting minutes
- Farm Bureau Organization, 1964, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  Mohawk Valley Beef Sales Inc., International Harvester Farm Magazine Spring 1964
- Newspaper: the Grape Belt, 1946-52, 1946-52 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Newspaper: the Grape Belt, 1953-60, 1953-60 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- New York Marketing Legistlation 1957, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Hearing Marketing Agreement Rules, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Court Decisions Apple Marketing Orders, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- H.R. 6983 Resnick Bill, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Upstate Agreement, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Long Island Agreement, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Potato Marketing Agreement, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Marketing Service: Part 970 Irish Potatoes Grown in Maine, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Potato Marketing Agreements, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Reports to Commodity Committee, 1957-62 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Improved Crop Reporting, 1957-58 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Commodity Conference Atlanta City, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Commodity Questions to Counties, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Annual Farm Bureau Meeting and Commodity Conference in Binghamton, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Commodity Conference, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Commodity Conferences - Annual Meetings, 1957-59 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Reports from Counties, 1958-60 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Organization of Commodity Department, 1956-61 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Commodity Committee Meetings, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- National Farmers Organization, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- List of Commodity Organizations, 1957-1965 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Commodity Department Reports to Board, 1958-60 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- 1956 Commodity Committee, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- General Commodity, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Tomato Study Committee, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Grower Processor Relations, 1957-60 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Vegetable Research by Cornell University, 1958-60 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- AFBF Accomplishments, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Onion Meeting, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Sugar Beets, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Potato Freight Rates, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Potato Controls, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Grades - Potatoes for Processing, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- GLF Potato Study, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Potato Conference at Syracuse, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Special Potato Commodity Meeting, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 38)